Created and Encoded by --  Bokutox -- of  www.YIFY-TORRENTS.com. The Best 720p/1080p/3d movies with the lowest file size on the internet.
Answer the phone!
No answer.
Keep trying. I'm sure
he's on his way back from...
Definitely on his way.
Why doesn't anybody
answer the phone?!
- Hello?
- James, you are so dead.
Shit!
Sorry!
Excuse me. James Clayton. Sorry I'm late.
I had a water bed emergency.
Bill Rudolph, Dell.
Nice to meet you.
Can I borrow your computer?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Hi, guys.
Hey.
It's here somewhere.
Here we go. All right.
At 7:00 this morning,
sound asleep,
I heard this cracking noise - ripping wood.
I figure it's part of this logging dream
I'm having,
but, no, the bed
is falling through the floor.
Our program uses
existing wireless technology...
Which we modified,
transforming it into
a completely new program.
- And what do you call it?
- "Sp@rtacus."
Why is that?
It was named after
the revolt...
Of the slaves.
Wireless Webcast.
We have that.
"Sp@rtacus" turns
any specified broadcast terminal
into its slave.
We control the program.
Watch.
Take a look. Pick a screen.
Hello, Bill Rudolph.
Hey, who is this guy?
Somebody's hacking in.
What is this?
This is wonderful.
Thank you.
Can you put our logo
on the Sony booths?
Sure, for the right price.
- We'll talk, yeah?
- Yeah.
Good.
Thank you.
Hey.
- What would you like?
- I would like to teach you something.
OK. I'm pretty busy right now.
James, the most important
thing you need to know
is that you don't know shit.
What you see,
what you hear.
Nothing is
what it seems.
Drink?
Martini.
Sure.
That's how it begins, you know.
Call will come in a day or two.
His name is John Medica.
He's head of R&D for Dell.
He's gonna invite you out
for martinis.
Before long,
you're gonna be working
out of Advanced Encrypting
in Bethesda.
Five years, you'll get
your first annual trip to Texas.
You got a wife by then,
.5 kids, 200K a year,
and that's it,
that's the whole show.
Then you're dead.
And it all started because
of one nasty little martini.
So you're a recruiter.
That I am.
You're kidding.
Applications for the CIA
are up tenfold.
Would I have to kill anyone?
Would you like to?
Beer man. Heineken?
Yeah, just a sec.
All I know about the CIA is
that they're a bunch of fat,
old white guys who fell asleep
when we needed them most.
Oh, well, like I said,
you don't know shit.
I know what I know.
- Nice meeting you, James.
- You too.
Way I figure, you'll probably
go in the oil business,
like your daddy.
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Did you know my father?
James, I have recruited
and trained and served
with the best
our country has to offer
for over a quarter
of a century.
I am a scary judge of talent.
It's my gift.
I am recruiting you,
Mr Clayton.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm not exactly CIA material.
You have any idea
what CIA material is?
It's not me.
No? Well, I don't know.
You graduated
top of your class at M. I .T .,
majored in nonlinear cryptography,
scored off the charts
in your undergrad psych profile test.
Those are confidential.
Yeah, right.
You're agile, athletic, and...
And what?
You grew up overseas -
Uzbekistan, Brunei,
Venezuela.
Yeah, my father worked
for Shell awhile.
Your father died in 1990
in a plane crash in Peru.
What's your point?
What's my point?
What the hell you think
my point is?
My name is Walter Burke.
My number's on the sports page.
Give me a call.
I'll be here
till noon tomorrow.
Very dramatic, James.
I want to talk. Can we talk?
Yeah.
Where are you?
Well, you know the phone booth
you're calling from?
Yeah.
Turn around.
As you like it.
You're pretty confident.
Well...
Tell me about my father.
You already know, don't you?
I mean, that's why
you're sitting here.
You want answers,
you're in the wrong car, kid.
I only have secrets.
You can't trust your best friends,
your five senses,
only the little voice inside you
most civilians don't even hear.
Listen to that.
Trust yourself.
I think that's what
your father would have said.
Trust yourself, James.
Can I help you, sir?
James Clayton.
I'm here for an interview.
Just pull in there,
check in with security.
Thank you.
Hey, my name is James Clayton.
I'm here to see Walter Burke.
He's expecting me.
You can wait for him over there.
I'll page him for you.
James.
Hey.
Rule number one:
Don't get caught.
Those were good officers.
Good friends.
So, you ready to get started?
Sure.
Have six pull in tight on F-4.
All right,
now give me some angles,
both tests. Both tests.
Tighter.
It's a carbon copy.
F-4. Yank him.
You've been caught
cheating, pal.
Please leave.
Still got the eyes, Walter.
What's that story,
you saw some old woman
pushing a baby carriage?
And Walter sees the carriage
is riding a little low, so bam!
No questions,
blows grandma right out of her shoes.
Turned out she was Hamas,
and the whole thing was
stuffed with explosives.
She wasn't Hamas,
she was Abu Nidal.
Abu Nidal, that's right.
These war stories,
you just love them, don't you?
Uh, D-4.
Tell him to forget the chick
and finish the test.
Burke says, "Forget the chick
and finish the test."
How do upsetting problems
generally make you feel?
Upset.
And when you get angry,
do you have trouble
staying in control?
Sure.
How do you typically
deal with failure?
Badly.
Have you ever been
deliberately cruel to an animal?
- Yes.
- Please, elaborate.
For Christmas, I tied wool reindeer horns
to my dog's head.
Would you consider yourself
subjectively firm
or objectively flexible?
Metaphysically wrinkle-free.
Quickly. Would you rather
ride on a train,
dance in the rain,
or feel no pain?
Feel no pain.
I know I said the rain-dancing thing,
but feel no pain.
Thank you.
God, I hate this.
Hey.
Hi.
I'm James.
Layla.
Like the song.
Yeah.
That's a big coffee.
I'm a big girl.
Sure.
Is your name James Clayton?
James Douglas Clayton.
Just a yes-or-no answer.
Is your name James Clayton?
Yes.
You were born October 21, 1976?
Have you ever worked for
any foreign governments?
No.
Have you taken tranquillisers today?
Miami.
Mind if I sit here?
Sure.
Hey. Ronnie Gibson from D.C.
James Clayton from all over.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
You got any idea what those two
are speaking over there?
I think it's Farsi.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, Farsi.
Clear!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
What?
Some of these chairs are wired.
They catch you drifting
during this,
10,000 volts up your ass.
Bullshit.
All right.
- Good morning.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my name is Dennis Slayne.
I'm assistant director
of operations at Langley,
and I would like
to welcome you here
to the CIA Special
Training Facility,
affectionately known
as "the farm".
Now let me introduce to you
your senior instructor,
Mr Walter Burke.
Morning.
So, why are you here?
Why are you here?
It ain't the money.
A GS-15 pay grade officer,
yours truly,
I rake in about, what,
75 grand a year?
You can't buy
a decent sports car for that.
It ain't sex.
Hey, being here
won't get you laid.
Oh, you're a dental hygienist?
I'm a member of the CIA,
Moscow Station chief.
Hello?!
What about fame?
Our failures are known.
Our successes are not.
That's the company motto.
You save the world,
they send you to some
dusty basement at Langley,
give you a little lemonade
and cookies,
and show you your medal.
You don't even get
to take it home.
So it ain't money,
it ain't sex, it ain't fame.
What is it?
I say we are all here
in this room
because we believe.
We believe in good and evil,
and we choose good.
We believe in right and wrong,
and we choose right.
Our cause is just.
Our enemies everywhere.
They're all around us.
Some scary stuff out there.
Which brings us here
to the farm.
You have all just stepped through
the looking glass.
What you see, what you hear...
nothing is what it seems.
Mr Burke?
Hey.
I was just... I was hoping
maybe I could buy you a beer
and we could talk.
I have so many questions
about my dad.
You're making a mistake, son.
Let me remedy it.
I was on semicongenial terms with you
during your recruitment, for that reason -
I was recruiting you.
I'm not your friend.
I'm not your ally.
I'm your instructor period.
That enough talk?
Good morning. It's 0600.
All CTs report
to Common Area, 15 minutes.
Is everybody ready?
Morning.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Over the next few months,
we're gonna teach you
how to deceive,
role-play,
psychologically assess,
sell, exploit.
We're gonna hand you
the tools...
the black arts.
Not witchcraft - trade craft...
Ready! Fire!
Disguise, surveil, detect.
You will be able to kill
with a variety of weapons
or none at all.
You will night-parachute,
rappel from choppers,
learn dry and wet demolition,
learn tactical,
high-speed emergency driving.
You will become...
Bond. James Bond.
Thank you, Mr Clayton.
You're already role-playing.
That's good.
You're ahead of all of us.
Let's start with Clayton.
Why don't you take Zack?
Nice move.
Where the hell did
you learn how to do that?
Metro Dade Police Academy.
Are you a senior instructor
at the farm?
- Yes.
- True.
OK, if you look at the screens,
you'll see his pulse is even,
respiration normal,
pupils undilated -
signs of the truth.
Come on, rough me up.
Let's go! Rough me up!
Have you ever worn
women's clothing?
Who said that?
- Yes.
- True.
Were you ever stationed in Peru?
Yes.
True.
Is your name Walter Burke?
No.
True.
Let's do it.
Five!
Skid and holster!
Remove your targets!
Nintendo.
These are paper ants -
microphone transmitters.
They adhere equally well
to flesh or clothing,
and they're biologically manufactured,
so as soon
as they become separated
from their storage palate,
they begin to break down.
After 48 hours,
this bug consumes itself.
These are all live
surveillance devices...
digitised,
miniaturised transceivers,
audio and video.
You will conceal them
throughout the bug house.
Your objective is to gain entry,
install three bugs each,
and exit the bug house
without getting caught.
You will have eight minutes.
What do we got here, Walter,
a bunch of DS& T geeks,
or we got some quality
NOC people?
I don't know.
Anybody get out
of the bug house lately?
Not many.
Doesn't look like
it's gonna happen tonight.
Don't underestimate my people,
Dennis, please.
Usually by now,
you've tagged a NOC.
Must be one in this class.
Well, maybe yes, maybe no.
Who knows?
The Shadow knows.
I love this part.
Buenas noches, amigo.
You've just been blanketed.
- That's two down.
- Who's counting?
Buenas noches, amigo.
You've just been blanketed.
Attaboy.
Go!
Go, go!
Who was that?
- You OK?
- Yeah.
OK.
Some of you will not survive
the farm.
Some will be asked to leave.
Some will quit.
But those of you
who do graduate
will be sent to work
out of Langley
or embassies around the world
as official cover operatives.
That is, spies
with diplomatic immunity.
Now, every once in a while,
someone is selected to be
a nonofficial cover operative,
or N-O-C - NOC.
The NOC is the truest practitioner
of espionage...
always out there,
always alone, unprotected.
If you are caught, you will most likely
be tortured, shot, and/or hanged.
And here's the best part:
No one will ever hear about it.
You will become a star
on a wall,
a blank space in a book.
Now, I can just feel
all you Alphas out there
gunning for this position
as I speak.
So remember,
everything is a test.
Yeah? All right.
All right,
I can afford ten cents.
Yo, I'm out.
All right, I'll see you.
Come on, you're gonna fold,
Ronnie. Just get it over with.
- You're a Miami cop, right?
- Yeah.
So why don't you speak Spanish?
I do.
So where'd you learn Farsi?
Persian beat?
That's funny. No, night school -
Florida Atlantic University...
so I could get in here.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
- Ronnie.
- I'm out.
Well, looks like it's just me
and Sonny Crockett.
Sonny Crockett.
Is that the black guy or the white guy?
What are the girls like
on South Beach?
What do you want to do?
All right.
- I'll see your bet and raise you.
- $2 raises max, remember?
Come on, we're not playing
by the rules here on the farm.
Are we? Are we? Are we, Sonny?
That's fine by me.
OK. So...
Are my pupils dilated?
I could be bluffing.
Or it could just be dark in here.
What do you think?
OK, I'll give it to you.
I fold.
- What did you have?
- Hey! That's not how we play.
- Your deal.
- Hey, man, good game.
Well, well, well...
Looks like boys' night in, huh?
Kinda sad.
I'm gonna change all that.
Time for a field trip.
We got the van outside.
We're all going for drinks
at the Blue Ridge.
All right, your objective -
reach the parking lot
with an asset who intends
to have sex with you.
You want us to pick up a girl?
Well, five, actually...
one each.
Hi.
- Here you go, Kitty.
- Thanks, Barry.
Not interested.
Neither am I.
How's that?
Well, your personal interests
are of no concern to me.
I just got out of the joint.
And there's only one thing
I'm concerned with right now.
And what would that be?
What do you think?
Sounds like fun.
Excuse me a second.
Hey, what's going on?
What are you doing here?
What's it look like?
Looks like you're drunk.
Perceptive.
Is everything OK?
Yeah, everything's great.
All right.
See you tomorrow.
James...
They cut me. I'm out.
You're kidding.
I'm out of the program.
You're serious.
Did they say why?
They didn't say anything.
They just sit you down,
debrief you,
and then stick you
in some shit-bag motel.
Sorry, all I can think about
is throwing up.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I think I had too much tequila.
You know,
it's just that you and I
finally have
this chemistry moment,
you know, and I even have
a motel room
where we could go back and
have completely justifiable comfort sex,
but all I can think about
is not throwing up.
The room's spinning, right?
Yeah, like a top.
You should go home.
I'll call you a cab.
Come on. Come here.
Will you settle for taking
me home and tucking me in?
I wish.
Blue Ridge Bar, yeah.
Ten minutes? Thank you.
Cab will be here in ten.
- OK.
- Come on, wait with me outside, OK?
- I...
Come on.
Layla, let's wait inside.
It's cold.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Just wait.
Come on. I want to kiss you.
Tell me about it.
Thank you.
For what?
Op completed.
My op was to stop you
from completing yours.
Who said my op was complete?
- Lighten up, man.
- It's just an op.
Just doing her job, that's it.
God, I hate this guy.
You did your job. Good.
Are you a citizen
of the United States?
- Yes.
- True.
Are you in any way
affiliated with the CIA?
- No.
- It's false.
All right, let's break up
this dance team.
Clayton, switch places
with Zack here.
All right, we all know,
I believe,
what a lie is when we see it.
But a good interrogator
can also soften a subject,
you know,
knock them off-balance,
make them vulnerable.
Never know what you might get.
So fire at will.
Is your name Layla Moore?
Yes.
True.
Last night at the bar,
you said we had
chemistry together.
- Do we?
- What?
His interrogation.
Answer the man.
Simple question: yes or no?
I was undercover legend.
It was part of the op.
True.
You said you wanted to go home
and have comfort sex.
Did you?
You're abusing this exercise.
Did you want to have sex
with me last night? Yes or no?
No.
Would you do anything
to become a CIA officer?
Anything?
No.
- Layla!
- Stay away from me.
- Can I talk to you?
- There are limits, James.
You want to suck up to Burke,
do it on your own.
This isn't about Burke.
You won, OK? You got even.
How does it feel?
Huh?
God!
I pity the fool.
- Anyone I know?
- Maybe.
Let it go.
You first.
I don't know how I...
I don't belong here.
Come on, meant to do this, son.
You know more about me
than I do?
Hey, this bag knows more
about you than you do, James.
It's in you.
It's in your blood.
Mama Land's crabs
from the Circle's fourteenth
in Saigon...
best crabs in the world.
This place: second-best.
OK, why don't you just go ahead?
Go ahead and ask me.
Did you know him?
No.
I met him once.
Falklands, around '89.
What was he doing there?
Think, son.
I can't tell you specifics.
I just can't.
I can't even confirm
his mission.
I can't.
He used to tell me stories.
He'd say
when they'd hit one,
the desert would rain oil.
That's what he did, James.
He told stories.
Yeah.
And he lied.
That doesn't mean
he didn't love you.
What was he, really?
What did he do?
You gotta come off it, kid.
You really do.
Because you keep looking back,
you're gonna miss
your whole life.
It's a mystery you cannot solve.
Who is Edward Clayton?
Well, among many things,
he was James Clayton's father.
Also, he was someone else.
He was a spook, James.
Just like me.
Just like you.
Don't look now.
By the bar.
We're being followed.
- You serious?
- Yeah.
Sometimes these guys
just like to loiter around,
see if they can gain intel
on the farm.
I'll get someone on it.
Hey.
Looking good.
Yeah, but can I do it blindfolded
jumping out of a plane?
I bet you can.
Thanks.
It's probably not
the best time to apologise.
You don't have to apologise.
Can I?
Sure.
Here's how I'm gonna look at it.
We learned a lot about each other.
Yeah, the hard way.
Yeah, the hard way,
but still, at least we know.
OK.
So, now we're ahead of the game.
Is that it?
Exactly.
So what do we do?
Nothing.
Not here.
- Not now.
- No, not now.
One year from now,
where are you?
Probably waitressing
at Denny's.
Yeah.
When I was a kid,
my father would get out the atlas...
OK, today we practise
the art of surveillance.
Remember your training.
The person being followed
is the...
Rabbit.
Rabbit. The person doing
the following is the...
- Eye.
Behind the eye is the rest
of the surveillance team,
who cannot see the rabbit
but follow the eye.
As the rabbit travels,
the teammates will rotate themselves
into the eye position
so that the rabbit doesn't realise
he's being followed.
Rabbit, don't forget,
your choke points
help you to identify
who's on your tail.
And keep those cellphones off.
In the field, they act like homing devices.
All right? What do we do?
Improvise, modify,
adapt, overcome.
Let's go to work!
Turn your cellphone off?
Didn't bring it.
Good.
Hey, this looks like
a good choke point.
You're right.
- Let's hide here and wait, OK?
- Sure.
- James! James!
- Layla!
No!
James!
Let go of me!
I am a Diplomatic Corps trainee.
We know that you work
for the CIA.
The CIA.
I don't work for the CIA.
I think you do.
Enjoy your cold shower.
Hungry, Jimmy?
You guys make the best stuff.
You realise that no country
with a McDonald's
has ever attacked
the United States?
They teach you that at the farm?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You think this is a game, James?
I think it's a test.
No.
I'm sorry, my friend.
This is no test.
Everything is a test!
Everything is a test.
Good morning, James.
What are the names
of your instructors?
OK.
John is the wise guy.
Paul's the cute one.
George is pretty quiet.
And this new kid...
I can't remember his name.
Now I know why
she was begging for you.
You're funny.
Sorry if these stink.
She pissed herself.
Layla.
Layla?
Burke! You want a name?!
Burke! Burke!
I wanted you to see this.
I wanted you to see
what happens to someone
you know,
someone you care about,
so you won't forget.
What you should learn
from this exercise...
and learn it well...
rule number one:
Do not get caught.
Hey, buddy, you are
sweating your ass off.
I know. It's hot.
No, I mean, you're really
sweating from the ass.
I'm so ashamed.
Don't worry, pal.
You just need
a little help back there.
This is my secret.
Manpons?
It's like a cool spring breeze
blowing through your ass cheeks.
At this point, I'll try anything.
Hello, this is Bill Rudolph at Dell.
I'm not in right now,
but please leave a message at the beep.
I'll return your call
as soon as possible. Thank you.
Hey, Bill Rudolph,
thank you for calling me back.
It's James Douglas Clayton.
We met at MIT in Boston
at... we... Spartacus.
And I was with my family for a while,
but now I'm back, and I'm ready
to raise the bar with Sp@rtacus,
cos we can raise the bar
with Sp@rtacus and change things.
Will you call me...
Nice hit.
What the...
You mind?
My throat.
Let go. Now.
Now.
What...
I see you're living good.
Get some clothes on.
We'll take a drive.
- A drive?
- Yeah. I'll wait outside.
That booze is coming out
of your bones.
What am I doing here?
I'm done, remember? I'm out.
I don't have to play
your stupid games.
But you will, James.
You will play because
your particular engine...
what drives you, moves you,
motivates you...
desire to please
me.
All right, pull over.
Pull over the goddamn car!
All right! Go ahead, get out.
You lasted longer
on your interrogation exercise
than any CT has
in the last 15 years.
I broke!
Everybody breaks!
That's the point!
Damn thing doesn't stop
till you break.
Then why did I wash out?
You didn't!
That's why I'm here.
You're the NOC, James.
- Bullshit.
- The washout was faked.
You're the NOC.
I told you I was
a scary judge of talent.
Why me?
Get in here.
I don't believe this.
More farm mind games.
- Nothing is what it seems, na na na.
- No, no, no, no. School's out.
Open that glove compartment.
Go ahead.
Find out why you.
That's why you.
- Layla? Wh...
- Layla Moore,
raised from the age of three by Tom
and Susan Moore of Worcester, Mass.
However, her real last name
isn't Moore. It's Nasari.
Birth mother is Algerian,
father's French.
It's all there...
secret bank accounts,
phoney records, fake passports.
Layla's a sleeper.
She's a mole, James.
I don't believe it.
This is crazy.
How the hell
did she get into the farm...
We wanted her in.
We want her to burrow in
as deep as she can,
because then she'll lead us
to her handlers.
We know exactly what she wants.
It's who she's giving it to -
that's what we need to know.
Layla's gonna take us
right up the food chain.
I won't do it.
You won't do it?
James,
why do you think I came
to Cambridge to recruit you?
Nobody's chasing CTs any more.
I mean, our applications
are through the roof.
We needed you, James.
No accidents.
You and Layla were matched.
She's an orphan.
You're a young man
searching for a father.
You're both highly motivated,
you're both highly independent.
You even look good together.
We paired you at the farm, son.
We paired you, remember?
The Blue Ridge barhop?
The lie detector session?
The choke point test?
And it worked, didn't it?
She trusts you.
Loves you, maybe.
And you're gonna take
that trust and that love
and you're gonna use it
to find out who she's working for.
James...
My first posting was in Italy - Trieste.
A physics conference
met there every summer.
So I meet this local girl -
beautiful, sweet.
She's working for the Russian group
as a secretary.
Anyway, I did my job.
I worked her. I turned her.
Pretty soon, she's giving me
everything, you know...
I mean,
really high-grade stuff...
and I'm a hero.
But I'm still a kid, two years,
fresh out of Ocala, Florida.
I got this perfect Italian girl, and she's
crazy for me and we're falling in love.
I knew the Russians
were getting close to her.
I knew she was in jeopardy,
but material was valuable.
I could've warned her.
I could've saved her.
But the information
was more important.
You understand?
The information was more important
than she was,
more important than I was.
It is what we do.
I need to think about it.
Come on. "Think about it."
You got 24 hours.
- Burke here.
- OK.
I'll do it.
Iwo Jima Memorial - this is where
you tell me about duty and sacrifice?
No, this is where I have
my breakfast burrito.
Volente Brothers.
They're the best.
There you go. Thank you.
Try it. It's heaven.
So, what is she after?
You ever read Kurt Vonnegut?
Yeah.
- You read Cat's Cradle?
- Nah.
Well, in that book, the world ends
because in a chip of ice,
a molecule is discovered
that can turn all the water
it touches into ice.
Since all water
is interconnected...
that is, pond to stream,
stream to river,
river to lake, lake to ocean...
the entire world freezes and dies,
and that seed molecule
is called lce 9.
Ice 9.
Langley has invented
a computer virus
that can plug into
any electrical receptacle...
that is, the wall outlet
in your apartment...
using existing wiring
to spread right through
the entire national grid.
No firewalls, no protection.
- Jesus.
- That's it.
Our national defence, our national survival
depends on electronics.
You take that away, we're back in
the Stone Age with our enemies.
This was good.
Can I make it?
So close.
You're going to Langley.
Your cover story is that
you washed out of the farm,
but we love you.
You're a good boy, a patriot,
so we got you a low-level,
low-security gig.
But your real assignment
is to get close to Layla
and to stay close to her.
Find out who she's talking to.
Layla requested Cryptography,
so we gave it to her.
She's working at the Directorate
of Science and Technology in Langley.
Well, if she's
a new employee in Langley,
isn't surveillance on her 24/7?
They've got to find out
what she's up to.
Langley's security is all about
entry and exit - going in, going out.
- You are scoped, taped...
- Morning.
Tagged like no other
place on Earth,
but once you're on the inside,
the assumption is you belong there.
Langley's too big to watch.
We're a city, and as such, we are
vulnerable to betrayal from within,
always have been -
Ames, Nickelson, Howard.
So what have you got me doing?
We've given you
a low-level data-processing position
in the information
management centre...
not uncommon for CTs
who don't graduate the farm.
You'll love it.
- Mr Clayton?
- Hey.
- Rob Stevens, your supervisor.
- Nice to meet you.
- Welcome to CIA.
- Thank you.
The building we're going into
is totally secure.
No radio-wave transmissions
in or out.
Electronic devices -
computers, telephones...
even your voice
create vibrations
that a sophisticated laser pointer
in the building can read and translate.
I'll tell you, this card won't get you
into the good stuff,
but that little logo
definitely gets you laid.
Republican girls - hot.
Here we go. This is you.
The manual's
pretty self-explanatory.
Log in as much data as you can
without getting carpal tunnel.
- Any questions, I'm 1229.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
I'll see you over there.
James.
Layla. Hey.
What ar... You're here?
Yep. Data entry.
Not exactly
what I'd imagined, but...
After you left
we missed you at the farm.
Yeah.
Look, I'm late, so...
Right. OK.
It's good to see you.
Yeah. You too.
Take care.
- Hi, Frank.
- Hey, how's it going?
Good.
Take care.
- Thanks. See you tomorrow.
- Good night.
Hey, Joey. Cappuccino.
Sure.
James.
Hi.
Hey. Hey.
I'm not stalking you, I swear.
I come here all the time.
- How you doing?
- Good. You mind?
No, of course not.
- Thanks.
- Sure.
What are you reading?
- Good?
- Weird.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
So...
I'm in Science and Tech.
- Science and Tech?
- Yeah.
Not in the field?
The field is what you said
you always wanted.
Yeah, well,
found out it wasn't.
It's good to see you.
You too.
So, where you living?
The company found me
an apartment in Georgetown.
- What about you?
- I'm over in Adams Morgan.
When did you move down
from Boston?
A week ago. I drove down.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
See you soon.
Yeah. You want a ride?
- Nah, I got my truck.
- OK.
- All right. See you.
- Good night.
Good night.
OK, you re-established contact.
Now get into her office,
see if she's accessed
the program.
If she's got lce 9,
what's she doing with it?
She can't copy it.
Langley computers don't have disk drives
for exactly this reason,
and she can't print it out.
There are no printers.
Company policy.
DS& T is a secure area.
You're gonna need clearance.
I'll handle that.
Thank you, sir.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
James, a bunch of us
are going over to Señor Pepe's.
- Margarita Monday.
- Republican interns, huh?
Hi, this is Layla Moore.
I'm in a meeting until 4:30.
You can call me then
or leave me a message after the t...
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Mike? Black, two sugars. Right?
- Thanks.
Hey.
- Oh, Sharon...
- Yeah?
I still haven't gotten
those files I asked about.
It's all right.
I'll look for them.
- How was the date?
- It was great.
I just don't know where to go,
and I don't know...
You know, there's this Italian restaurant
down in Georgetown, and it's authentic.
- Hi.
- Hey.
You dropped these in my car.
Must've just slipped
out of your hand.
Nah.
I dropped them on purpose.
You trying to manipulate me?
Maybe.
It's working.
- Frank.
- Hey.
- Good night, Layla.
- Good night.
Layla. Wait up.
Here you go.
Allow me, madame.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Where's your car?
- Red pickup, over there.
- Nice. New?
- Newish. This your little baby?
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Night.
- See you tomorrow.
Hey, James?
Yeah?
I want to show you something.
That camera takes 30 seconds
to scan the room.
That one takes another
30 seconds on the opposite arc.
So if you stand right here,
you're ready to waltz one step,
you could have 40 seconds of complete
privacy where the cameras won't see you.
19, 18, 17...
Here?
Closer.
- Here?
- There.
Now we're completely private.
Ten, nine...
What were you thinking about
when you figured this out?
You.
Three, two, one, waltz.
We have 20 more seconds.
That's not enough time.
Layla?
Sorry it's so early, but...
I don't sleep.
Piss like a racehorse
every two hours.
Impossible. What do you got?
You were right about Layla.
Some of the lce program
is on her home computer,
but it's not all there yet.
She's taking it out in pieces
and putting it back together.
How's she getting it out of the building?
That's the question.
And more importantly,
who's she giving it to?
I want you to take this.
Open it somewhere later.
You know, no matter
how sure we are
about a person,
no matter how close or friendly
you think they are...
I know.
- I believe Layla's a traitor.
- Yeah.
- It's just...
- It's ugly.
This is an ugly business,
you know?
Can't pay us enough
for this kind of stuff,
and they don't.
The truth is,
at the end of the day,
it's what we do.
It's a job.
It's not who we are.
We decide who we are.
All right!
Morning, sleepyhead.
Sure, come right in.
Usually when a man ditches me
in the middle of the night,
he doesn't call the next day.
Imagine my surprise when
he's banging down the door.
Sorry. I couldn't sleep,
so I went to the gym.
Breakfast?
Yeah, sure.
I'm starving.
Hey, how about that breakfast
you promised me?
Cheese eggs -
my dad's specialty.
He called 'em heart stoppers.
The breakfast of champions.
Good?
So, do you still think about it?
The farm, I mean.
I wanted Burke to stop.
I told him to stop.
Nope. Not about that.
I mean the training.
Do you think it changes you?
Learning to lie, deceive.
Yeah, sure.
I mean, I definitely think
about things differently now.
I mean, every person I meet
is a possible mark.
Sure.
I got an idea.
Why don't we do
stupid tourist things today?
Come on, we can go and sit
on Lincoln's knee,
look at John Dillinger's penis.
I swear to God,
it's in the Smithsonian,
along with other weird Americana
like the Fonz's jacket.
What do you say?
I got to work.
Work? Wrong answer.
What are you gonna do on Saturday?
It's your taxpayers' dollars
in action, my friend.
You sure you got to go to work?
Yeah.
I'll see you tonight, right?
- See you later.
- Bye.
Gorgeous dog.
Hey, fella. How you doing?
- So nice to meet you.
- She's a sweetheart.
- She's pretty.
- Thank you very much.
- See you.
- Have a good day.
You can't park here.
The "A" train to St. Petersburg
is now boarding.
Stop! Freeze!
Freeze!
Zack.
Hey, you! Stop!
Stop!
Suspect's Caucasian and 5'10",
wearing green jacket.
The delayed "A" train from St. Petersburg
will be arriving in half an hour.
The "A" train from St. Petersburg
- Sorry.
- Hey!
Will be boarding
in 15 minutes at Gate "D".
No sign of the suspect yet.
Green jacket, male, Caucasian.
- Affirmative, 21.
- 5'10", brown hair.
This is the Shady Grove Red Line.
Next stop...
Burke here.
Zack's dead.
I killed him.
Where are you?
He... he was working with Layla.
- Jesus.
- James, just tell me what happened, now.
She met him.
I saw them.
Zack attacked me.
I killed him.
Well, I have to pull you out, then.
I have to get somebody else
on this thing.
Look, let me do it.
This is what I trained for.
You said so yourself.
She's probably going back
to Langley to finish the job,
and if she's not, I'll intercept her.
I'll get the material, and we'll meet.
I can do this.
Look, please. Trust me.
All right.
I'll come into town.
I'll meet you in the Navy Yards
near "M" street,
8:00.
OK. Navy Yards,
"M" street, 8:00.
Thank you. Have a good weekend.
Layla, pull over
the goddamn car!
Pull over the goddamn car!
James, what do you want?!
Shit!
Don't move! Don't move!
Open the door! Open it!
Don't move!
Unscrew the bottom. Do it!
Now!
OK.
Go.
I'll tell them you surprised me.
Get as far away as possible.
What?
I don't know why you turned.
I don't care.
James, I didn't turn. You did.
I know who I'm working with.
I know what I'm doing. Do you?
Look, stop it!
I know everything!
Your mission, the intel,
your parents.
James, I'm CIA.
My mission was to assess
the security protocols at Langley
to see if I could get
the data out of the facility.
I did.
But, Jesus, James,
it's probably bullshit anyway.
It can't be real.
It was a test.
They couldn't take the risk.
Nothing was real!
You are a traitor,
a double agent.
I followed you.
Zack had your note.
Zack is working with me.
Zack is CIA.
Zack is dead!
What?
James, Zack is CIA. He's...
He fired on me. I shot him.
- What?
- I killed him.
Look, I am on
a CIA-sanctioned mission.
No.
Layla, I didn't wash out of the farm.
I'm the N-O-C . I'm the NOC.
No, Zack was. Zack was the NOC.
No, this is a sanctioned mission.
I received...
- James.
- ...orders from my control.
No.
Layla, go. Get out of here.
James, please, just...
just listen to me, OK?
Just keep the gun on me.
Just keep it on there, OK?
And give me your free hand.
Just give it to me, please.
OK? Just feel my pulse, OK?
Look at my pupils.
See if I'm lying.
Now, listen, I am not a double.
I work for the CIA.
Zack works for the CIA.
We are on
an agency-sanctioned mission.
James...
Go.
Run far away. Disappear, Layla.
Disappear, Layla!
No! James!
- Hello?
- Layla?
Listen to me. The program you stole
from Langley, it is real.
- No, it can't be real.
- Listen to me.
This is what I do -
programs, code.
- James, where are you?
- It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
I think we started lying to each other
almost as soon as we met, so
there's no real reason
to believe any of it was true.
But I'm gonna anyway, OK?
- Time's up.
- James...
James!
- All right.
- Jeez!
You better start telling me
what the hell is going on.
Oh, man! My dick's on fire.
Layla says I'm a double agent!
- Yeah.
- All right, Zack's dead!
- What the hell is going on?
- Calm down.
No!
Open that glove compartment.
I got napkins in there.
And put away that stupid gun.
It's only blanks.
Come on, I'm wet here.
Come on.
Start talking.
Congratulations.
You passed your final test.
- Test?
- These pants are ruined.
What do you mean, test?
Everything's a test, remember?
Nothing is what it seems.
Well, what about lce 9?
That a test?
Toss it. Keep it as a souvenir.
It's gibberish.
- No way. No, it's not.
- Yeah, yeah.
The squibs that went off on Zack
when you shot him.
- What?
- Nothing's real.
Squibs?! No, I watched him die!
- You did?
- Yes!
Well, I want you to tell him that,
cos we're meeting him
in half an hour for drinks.
You tell him you watched him die.
I'd like to see his face.
I'd like to see your face.
All right?
Who gave you the gun?
Who gave you the gun?! Me.
No one's using real bullets, remember?
Everything is role-play.
Remember?
Where were you when
we were going through all this?
Put that gun out of my face.
If you want to point it at me,
point it at my chest, will you?
Cos they're blanks in there.
Just shoot, OK?
Point it at my chest
and go ahead.
Get it out of your system
so I can go home and change my pants.
Go ahead, shoot. Fire.
Just shoot it!
Pull the trigger.
Go ahead, try it.
Come...
James?
Let me explain!
I don't know
what went wrong.
You seemed like
the perfect recruit.
I mean, you were smart.
You were motivated.
Slayne, some of the others
thought you tried too hard
to please me.
When you couldn't,
you just snapped.
You know?
I tried to help you, James.
Got you a job at Langley
after you washed out of the farm.
But that wasn't good enough
for you, was it?
You got bitter.
You got angry.
"CIA is just a bunch
of fat, old white guys
who fell asleep
when we needed them most."
Remember that?
I got it on tape.
You see where this whole thing
is going, James?
Go, go, go!
You called me.
You wanted to talk.
You said you had something
to show me.
Bragged to me about how
you were gonna screw the company,
screw us all.
You even shot at me
in the car, shot at me.
And we fought
and you hit me.
- Well...
- Shit!
I got my cover.
You got yours?
You killed a man, son.
Killed by your hand.
You've got no way out but me.
You're gonna have to negotiate.
The lce 9 program isn't real.
It's a fake!
Oh, no. It's real.
Switched it myself.
Remember?
Once you're in Langley,
you can do anything.
- It's getting it out that's a bitch.
- I could delete it right now. Erase it all!
That's how to play the game, James.
Your daddy would be proud
of you - that kind of talk.
All right, that's enough.
You stop.
You don't talk about him.
You do not mention his name!
- Sensitive.
- You're a liar, a traitor!
He was none of those things.
Well, he wasn't in the CIA.
Maybe that's why.
I mean, now that we're letting it all
hang out, airing our laundry.
- Bullshit.
- No. He didn't work for us.
Bullshit. He did.
He worked for the company.
Yeah. Shell Oil.
Sorry, kid. Dreams die hard.
So, now what?
Am I supposed to fall apart?
Is that it?
Hand you over the computer
with my desire to please, Burke?
Well, it's an option.
Well, here's another option:
Shoot me. Go ahead.
Now, you sound like
a sore loser to me.
Don't you appreciate
the complexity of this thing?
James, come on, man.
I'm working without a net here.
And I pulled it off, too.
I'm clean. You're not.
I don't want to hurt you.
I just want the computer.
All right,
now, where might that be?
First, tell me why. Why me?
Why? How? When?
You're like a bunch of baby birds
with your beaks open,
waiting for me
to vomit out answers.
Why me?!
I needed a partner.
You needed a father.
What is the principal job
of a CIA officer?
You develop an asset,
you work 'em, then you turn 'em.
I found you. I worked you.
How much? How much did it cost
to buy the great Burke?
$3 million. That's cash.
This is America.
Now, are you gonna show me
that computer?
All right?
Don't make me kill you, son.
It ain't worth it.
It's all about the money.
You think you know me?
You think you know me,
don't you?
You don't.
There was a time...
There's this parish priest
goes up to the pope,
drops down on his knees,
starts weeping,
asking forgiveness.
"Holy Father, Holy Father,
what am I to do?"
"What am I to do?"
"I do not believe in God any more."
You know what the pope said?
"Fake it."
I couldn't fake it anymore.
So now I'm gone.
You get it?
And so are you if you don't
give me the computer.
Now. Now!
All right!
You want your computer?
It's over there behind my coat,
under the stairs.
It's all yours. Take it.
Showtime. Went to Langley.
It's all over. They've heard it all, Burke.
Freeze!
Hold it there!
Well,
will you look at this?
27 years, I'm finally
in the spotlight, right?
What do you know?
What do we do now?
Come get my gun
or you just want to hang me?
Hang the traitor.
You ready for that, Slayne?
I hear you.
"Why'd you sell us out, Burke?"
I sold you out.
No way!
Jesus Christ.
27 years neck-deep in shit!
Sell you out?
Did I do my job?
I ask you, you do your job?
I hand you the target.
I tell you who and where.
What do you do?
All you got to do is act.
Do you do your job? No!
I'm obsolete!
I'm irrelevant!
Me! Shame on you!
You yanked me home!
You shoved me out in the woods!
- Some lvy League prick...
- Jesus Christ.
- Who's afraid of having dinner in D .C...
- The target is Burke.
Because of street crime
is judging my worth,
shoving me in the fucking...
Put it down, Walter.
They came for you.
Yeah.
The line to the CIA was a fake.
You never told 'em.
No.
You did.
Nothing is what it seems.
God damn it, Walter.
You got me.
Hand in the cookie jar.
You got to give me one thing.
I'm a scary judge of talent.
- Here goes nothing.
- No.
- Bye-bye.
- No!
No!
All right.
Clayton, you ride with me.
We're gonna need
to debrief you at Langley.
James?
Let's go, Clayton.
You all right, Clayton?
Yeah.
Forgot to turn your cellphone off.
That's how we tracked you -
your cellphone.
I didn't forget.
I knew she'd do her job.
Well, I'll remember to team
you two up together next time.
Next time?
You were born to do this, James.
It's in your blood.
Best watched using Open Subtitles MKV Player